[
    {
        "question": "1) [TEAM] - Who is the Founder and lead visionary of the project?",
        "options": [
            "Josh",
            "Petrolad",
            "Norman",
            "Alex",
            "Jonathan"
        ],
        "answer": "Norman"
    },
    {
        "question": "2) [TEAM] - What is the role of Mr.'Alex'? ",
        "options": [
            "Blockchain Developer",
            "Artist",
            "Community Manager",
            "Lead Writer",
            "Founder"
        ],
        "answer": "Lead Writer"
    },
    {
        "question": "3) [BACKGROUND] - Clementine is ",
        "options": [
            "an Artist",
            "a Singer",
            "a Gamer",
            "a Dancer",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "an Artist"
    },
    {
        "question": "4) [BACKGROUND] - Clementine draws",
        "options": [
            "sketches of animals",
            "abstract arts",
            "her nightmares and dreams",
            "about her future",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "her nightmares and dreams"
    },
    {
        "question": "5) [GAME] - Clementine's game is going to be a",
        "options": [
            "single player game",
            "multiplayer, action packed game",
            "just a card game",
            "simple strategy game"
        ],
        "answer": "multiplayer, action packed game"
    },
    {
        "question": "6) [GAME] - Game is going to be a ",
        "options": [
            "free to play game",
            "subscription based",
            "paid only"
        ],
        "answer": "free to play game"
    },
    {
        "question": "7) [GAME] - In game Rebels better with ",
        "options": [
            "healing",
            "weapons and at hand to hand combat",
            "tracking enemies",
            "defending"
        ],
        "answer": "weapons and at hand to hand combat"
    },
    {
        "question": "8) [Token] - Do clementine NFTs will focus on Utilities ",
        "options": [
            "Nope",
            "Yes, they do"
        ],
        "answer": "Yes, they do"
    },
    {
        "question": "9) [Token] - How many number NFTs are going be of each character",
        "options": [
            "1",
            "100",
            "500",
            "1000",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "500"
    },
    {
        "question": "10) [General] - How creates the art",
        "options": [
            "A single guy",
            "A freelance artist",
            "30-40 individuals"
        ],
        "answer": "30-40 individuals"
    }
]